

Sarmathi K

Date of birth: 19/06/1999 | **Nationality:** Indian | **Gender:** Female |

Phone number: (+91) 9500397028 (Mobile) | Email address:

sarmathi1906@gmail.com | Website:

https://ppchennai.vercel.app/Sarmathi/MY_BLOG/blog.html | Twitter:

https://twitter.com/Sarmathik83997?t=4Li7TU0JXPnV4x QM5vZ2w&s=08

Whatsapp Messenger: https://whatsapp.com/dl/

Address: 6/318, Periyar nagar,, Manavadi, Karur., 639005, Karur, India (Home)

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm Sarmathi k, i am an experienced joiner with well developed skills and experience in front-end developer with a knack for creating Enthrallment and visually appealing web experiences. Am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills. I have strong ethic and am very motivated towards what i do when my off day. I enjoy working with others and am always happy to help. I possess knowledge in various testing methodologies of ChatGpt and a deep understanding of AI and ML concept. Additionally, my excellent networking and team- working skills enable me to collaborate effectively with other developers, designers, to achieve project goals. Furthermore, I am good at English and German. I am a hard working, honest individual. I am outgoing and tactful, and able to listen effectively when solving problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

25/06/2022 - CURRENT Chennai, India

FRONT-END DEVELOPER PEPPER PROGRAMMING AB

- 1. Providing maintenance support for customer Web Pages which are in live environment.
- 2. As a skilled Full Stack Developer with experience in UI, tools like HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT and UX, tools like Figma, Canva, Adobe Express, Framer and GitHub. I have created my own blog by using WordPress. I am confident that I can make a significant contribution with our team. Regarding Al Engineer, I possess knowledge in various testing methodologies of ChatGpt and a deep understanding of Al and ML concept.
- 3. I am proficient in Agile Scrum methodology, which enables me to develop high-quality applications while ensuring that they meet project timelines and requirements. Additionally, my excellent networking and team- working skills enable me to collaborate effectively with other developers, designers, to achieve project goals.

07/01/2022 - 25/10/2022 Karur

GRADUATE APPRENTICE TRAINEE POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA PVT LTD.

- Worked in an intern position for Power Grid maintenance and new service provisioning cases.
- I have done more field works and experienced with shutdown &testing tools.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

08/07/2016 - 17/05/2020 Tiruchencode, India

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING Vivekanandha College of Engineering for Women

Website https://vivekanandha.ac.in/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **TAMIL**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	B2	C1	B2
GERMAN	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Java Script | React Js | Digital Marketing | Figma | Canva | Agile methodology | github | ChatGpt | Generative AI | MongoDB | Node JS | Express js | Vue js

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

10/07/2023 - 13/07/2023

My_Blog I created my own portfolio including myself, projects and blogs. You want to know me just touch the link.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Reading books When I started to read books, I thoroughly came out from the live world. Because I do deep focus when I am reading books. Reading habits to change my inner thoughts of inferiority complex and making my mind to refreshed and shows happiness of my face.

Painting When I am bored I start to paint myself off to our house wall. I am not painting professionally but I am a professional painter in myself.